It is correct. I am doing two things. I have started
the recording,
number one, and I readmitted
both Amanda and Nick Levine.
Okay.
>> So the only two people in the waiting room.
All right that was 11:08.
Amanda went to sleep.
>> Seriously I was worried about it. There's Amanda.
Okay.
So now that Amanda and Nick are back on,
let's sit there and move this forward.
In accordance
with Section 3A of the employment agreement between the town of Andover and Eric Anderson having reviewed the deliverables in Appendix A of the same, I motion to award
$7,120
to the town administrator to be added to his pay on the week ending June 20. Additionally, per the terms of the agreement, Eric Anderson is also awarded
2% of
the PGTTA grant for
sixteen thousand six hundred and fifty five point three six dollars by the Public Utilities Regulatory Commission for a total of $333
The total I
>> would just amend your motion. I would accept it but amend it
that
the additional compensation per the contract cannot be paid until the completion of the grant.
>> It's technically until the grant money is received
and we have that $16,000
in our checking account.
>> I thought it but you're responsible for completion so as long as we're saying that it's completed
as part of the agreement you have to complete the agreement. You have to actually
go through and administer
the
grant.
Okay, that's fine. I can live with that.
>> He's received the money.
But it's not been spent. So it hasn't been administered. It's an administrative fee. That's the agreement.
>> I'm not trying to be clear. I just want to follow the contract.
No,
>> can live with that. How about Jeff Murray with our lawyer?
What's the wording of the contract?
It's
the lawyer.
>> What
is the paragraph? What's the paragraph say? I actually sent you the contract
>> sub in attorney if you'd like to look at it it's in your email.
>> Okay
Eric are you okay if you need
another couple months but Eric it should be be aware
that that is going get paid as soon as that that Absolutely.
Absolutely. As soon as it's done.
Okay.
So so we'll go back and,
>> Hold on. Hold on.
Here's what it says. The employee will become entitled to a bonus for any such grant
as soon as the grant funds are received by the town,
but any payments owed to him will be made at the end of the calendar quarter,
which would be the twentieth. So he's entitled.
>> Do we have a clawback if he doesn't complete it?
It's
Come on, Adrian. You're
>> amending that contract next year. He mustn't complete it. I'll pay the town with $333.
Go on Adrian pay the man. All right fine.
>> All right so
I was trying to finish my motion which is not necessary
and I was trying to sit there and say
for a total amount
of $7,453
Second.
>> You go.
Would you like me to read it again?
No? No. It's ready.
Any further discussion?
No.
All those in favor?
Aye.
>> All five of us, that's excellent work. You were waiting for that abstain weren't you? I was.
Five zero.
Okay,
I'm making the motion to adjourn.
Please.
Do you have cake for everyone? We'll be over.
>> We only got a little little acaribao cake. I'm sorry. I had to leave the meeting for a little bit to sing happy birthday to my son. We heard you didn't
mute it we all heard you singing. That
>> is awesome I can't wait to see that on television.
>> I had my birthday on June 3 and I didn't have
the dairy bar ice cream cake this year. I was depressed because it was cold. What
flavor did you get?
>> I had to have regular cake. I'm sorry. Wait a second. Wait a dairy bar preference. Wait a second. This is Jeff Murray's birthday month. We have to sing happy birthday. We need to know what cake he wants when it gets back open.
>> The dairy bowl. I think it's all the same. They have all the same cakes.
>> Doesn't offer. We're singing happy birthday to Jeff before we adjourn so. Happy
>> birthday
to
you.
You.
Are you one? Are you two?
>> Yay. Now you're making me feel bad because you didn't sing me happy birthday on my birthday. When was your birthday?
March 2.
Oh, no.
Happy birthday, At
your age, you don't point out birthdays anymore.
I do.
>> I'm putting it I don't know about you guys, but I'm putting it in my phone.
That was third.
>> I won't even put the year.
That's okay. Now I got to go with Scott. And you know what? The only one I'm missing is Paula. I'm missing Amanda too. I gotta get that one.
>> You guys sang to me on was it I don't know if it was on my birthday the meeting January 14.
I expect I expect a car. We did.
>> Yeah. We did. I gotta see it all. It was so bad we all were trying to
put it on our table.
God that was March 3 or March 2.
Second.
What year is that?
1956.
'63.
>> I love that. Good job Scott. All right I motion to adjourn.
All second. All
right all those in favor. Right. Eric
>> thank you very much for everything. Amanda thank you very much for everything. We appreciate it. You're very welcome. All right. See you guys. All right. See you folks. Good night.